hapmedia.com 2012-12-31

# HapMedia.com - A CPA CPL CPS Affiliate Network

HapMedia has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering, use and dissemination practices solely for the web site located at www.hapmedia.com (the "Site"). By using or accessing the Site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE. Use of the services on the Site are subject to other terms and conditions. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
We do not collect personal information about Site users unless such information is voluntarily provided by the user. Our registration forms require users to provide certain contact information such as name, contact information, email address, tax ID number and other information. This information is used by HapMedia and its affiliated companies to provide the services you select through the Site. Except as set forth in this policy, the information is not sold or rented to third parties. If you no longer wish HapMedia to use your personal information, see the Choice/Opt-Out section below to remove your information. 

We may need to disclose personal information when required by law and when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us or to assist in the investigation of any potential fraud. We may also disclose personal information in connection with a sale, merger or reorganization of HapMedia. 

**Collection of Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
We may collect non-personal information (or aggregate information) during your use of our Site, including IP address, pages viewed, click-stream data and browsing habits. Non-personal information may be shared with third parties who are not affiliated with HapMedia. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual's computer that allows HapMedia to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in HapMedia's database. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. Individuals who use the Site need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Site. 

**Choices /Opt-Out**  
To opt-out of any of a mailing from HapMedia, you may follow the opt-out procedures set forth in our emails to you or send an email to us at support@hapmedia.com. However, we are not responsible for removing your personal information from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this policy. 

**Reviewing Your Information**  
If you would like to review and update or correct the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you online, or if no longer wish to continue your service with us, simply send your request here . 

**Links**  
This Site contains links to other sites. HapMedia is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. Please read the privacy policies of these linked sites, because their privacy practices may differ from ours. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. However, if at any time in the future we plan to use personal information in a way that differs from this policy, we will post such changes here and provide you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. 

**Legal Statement**  
Use of this Site is governed by, and subject to, the legal notices contained in our Legal Statement and other terms and conditions that are made available to you. Your use, or access, of the Site constitutes your agreement to be bound by these provisions. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE. 

**Effective Date**  
This privacy policy is effective and was last updated on February 10, 2009. 

**Contacting HapMedia**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact us here.
